My wife,
you
must
live
well.
Live on.
To think they brought in the guards.
What a pity for such a large stronghold.
Wuyou City
needs to be cleaned up.
Heizi.
Meng Qian.
Didn't I tell you to go home?
Why are you still at the pier?
Just because you tell me to go home,
doesn't mean I will.
I told you,
guiding those people is a death wish.
I wanted you to go home and live well.
Meng Qian,
I've always
refused to accept you.
We are both at Sangjia Wazi
trying to make a living.
Why is it
that you have the reputation?
I...
I don't accept it.
I just wanted
to pull off a big job.
What big job could you pull off?
You really are...
I wanted
to help them kill the Master of Wuyou Cave.
Then I'd surely get famous and outshine you.
I didn't expect
the Master of Wuyou Cave
to be
killed now.
But I
didn't even
get famous.
What did you just say?
The Master of Wuyou Cave was killed?
Who killed him?
Heizi.
Heizi!
Your Highness.
There was a fierce battle at the Xishuimen Pier just now.
The Cave Master's double
is dead.
Who did it?
It was a melee among several parties,
but the real mastermind
should be the Knife Seller's arch-enemy.
Never mind.
Since he wants to create the illusion of the Wuyou Cave Master's death,
we will grant his wish.
Since when is it Zhou You's business to catch rebels?
A young lady went missing from the Zhao Manor.
Li Yi'an asked Zhou You for help.
When Li Yi'an came to the capital this time,
the Emperor had Zhou You escort her out of the palace.
Li Yi'an
probably got to know Zhou You because of that
and asked him for help.
If there really are rebels,
tell your subordinates to be smart.
Don't give away the credit for nothing.
Yes.
Tonight in Dongjing City,
there are constant disturbances.
Tomorrow is the Lantern Festival.
This Fanlou
will probably experience another shock.
The unrest around Xishuimen Wharf
is said to be a melee between several rebel factions.
You could suggest to the Emperor
that tomorrow night
he refrain from visiting Fanlou for now.
Chen Wu.
Let go.
Let go!
What are you doing?
Why did you betray us?
How did I betray you?
Dare you say you didn't lead these guards here?
Dare you say you didn't report us?
Why would I report you?
My sister's life is still in your hands.
Am I crazy to report you?
Then how did these guards get here?
The guards are catching assassins and rebels.
Naturally, they came because they found out where you are.
Dare you say
you're not going to Fan Restaurant to assassinate His Majesty?
Dare you say it?
Captain Chen.
Let him go.
Brother Meng stopped us tonight.
I thought
you already knew.
I was guessing.
You never said from beginning to end
going to Fan Restaurant on Lantern Festival,
what exactly you are going to do.
Even if you knew,
what good
would it do you?
I didn't want to know at all.
But you threatened me with my sister.
Now that you know,
what can you do?
I...
I have been tortured by you for two days.
Could it be that you know
something else?
If you go to Fan Restaurant
not to assassinate His Majesty,
just say it.
Otherwise,
you will face greater resistance.
If we say it,
what then?
If you say it,
I can take you to see someone.
You.
Who knows if you'll betray us again?
I've said it several times.
My sister's life is in your hands.
Why would I betray you?
Believe it or not.
Anyway, that person is very powerful.
Enemies or allies,
you choose.
Don't be anxious, Brother Meng.
I also think
you make sense.
In our plan,
we are indeed missing the part of the people around His Majesty.
If Brother Meng can help us get through this,
that would be best.
But,
this ally you mentioned,
is he from the government?
My Lord.
I have something to tell you.
Where were you for the two hours
after the Yunxiang Restaurant incident?
Do you want to personally catch
the assassins who tried to kill His Majesty?
What do you mean?
I met those people from Mount Liang
outside Yunxiang Restaurant.
I brought them here.
What did you say?
If you want to catch the real assassins, my Lord,
you'd better see them first
before deciding whether to make a move.
What nonsense are you talking about?
They
might not necessarily want to assassinate His Majesty.
Sister.
Meng just said
you brought the guys from Liangshan here.
Yes.
Sister.
Please invite them in.